

MARK REA

PROGRAMMER



CONTACT



Phone

+64 22 171 8161



Email

markrea151002@gmail.com



Address

New Zealand - Lake Terrace Taupo 3330



EDUCATION

2015 - 2020

Hight School, Núñez Ponte, Anaco

Courses

Python and Web

development

- UK boost camp
- International course



LANGUAGE

- English
- Spanish
- Italian



ABOUT ME

Hello my name is Mark Rea and I am a New Zealand citizen, I left New Zealand when I was young and I lived the most of my life overseas, I had a few jobs in a coffee shop, restaurant, electronic store and as a freelancer, I have returned to New Zealand to complete my education and experience for the goal i have.



WORK EXPERIENCE (OVERSEAS)

Barista and Pastry

Alimentos Mark/Mokafe

Responsible for all the desserts of the store and experienced barista in charge of the cafe

Web Developer and Salesman

Inv.Niarg

2020 - 2022

Manager of the store and I make sure I have inventory control, in addition to offering good customer service and make a complete website for the store.

Web Developer

Servicios H.G July 2022 - 2023

I built a fully responsive, creative and interactive website for the company



WORK EXPERIENCE (NZ)

Kitchen and maintenence

Mc.Donalds/Taupo 2023(July) - present

Reponsible of the kitchen at some points and in charge to keep my working space clean and prepared for the next shift.



MY SKILLS & EXTRAS

Python	Photoshop
HTML	Design



CSS

MY REFERENCE

Andrea Gloria

Servicios H.G / Director / CEO +58 412-4992413

Liseth Pérez

Grupo Rizos/Alimentos Mark / Administradora / CEO

+58 414-8398963